Janice has a question.
Who of the six of you...
질문 있어요
여섯 명 중 누구는
... has slept with
who of the six of you?
여섯 명 중 누구랑
자본 적 있겠죠?
Wow, it's like a dirty math problem.
와! 더럽게 복잡하네
유감스럽지만
아무도 없을걸요
I'm sorry, the answer there
would be none of us.
몇 년 동안 술 먹고
실수도 한번 안 했어요?
Over the years, none of you
ever got drunk and stupid?
그건 다른 문제죠
Well, that's really
a different question.
I can't believe a group of people
who spends this much time together...
난 이렇게 맨날 붙어다니면서
추한 꼴 한번 안 보인다는 게
... has never bumped uglies.
좀 신기해요
There was that one time
Monica and Rachel got together.
모니카랑 레이첼은
한동안 좀 그랬죠
What?
뭐?
'한동안'까진 아냐
Excuse me, there was no "time."
Okay, but let's say there was.
'잠깐'으로 해두지
How might that go?
또 보고 싶은걸
알았어요
다시 물어볼게요
Well then answer me this:
Have any of you ever almost...?
거의 할 뻔한
적은... 있겠죠?
- 커피 더 마실 사람?
- 너 신발 예쁘다
-Anybody need more coffee?
-Hey, there's a dog out there!
밖에 웬 개지?
The One With the Flashback
3년 전
-That is so unfortunate.
-What?
- 이걸 어째?
- 왜?
벌거숭이 귀여운 남자가
살이 찌고 있어
Cute Naked Guy's
starting to put on weight.
잠깐 나갔다 올게
I'll be back in just a minute.
I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks
on the phone.
피비, 전화기에 립스틱
자국 묻혀서 미안해
네가 뭘 묻혔다고 그래?
You didn't leave lipstick marks
on the phone.
Then it must have been you. Bye.
그럼 네가 묻혔겠구나
안녕!
잘 가라!
Bye-bye.
이래서 나간 거야
-That's why I moved out.
-Hey, while we're on that...
네가 여기 안 사는 거
언제쯤 얘기하려고?
...when are you gonna tell my sister
you don't live here anymore?
On some level, she already knows.
쟤도 어느 정도 알 거야
걘 네가 밤에 몰래 나갔다
아침에 들어오는 거 몰라
She doesn't know you sneak out
every night...
...and back every morning...
네가 1주일 째 할머니 댁에서
잔 것도 모른다구
...and that you've been
at your grandmother's for a week.
그 정도까진 모르나보지
Okay, well, maybe not on those levels.
I'm never gonna find a roommate.
Ever.
룸메이트 구하는 거
못해먹겠다
좋은 사람이 없어?
Nobody good?
흰 족제비를 데려오질 않나
그것도 여러 마리!
There was the guy with the ferrets.
That's plural.
침도 뱉더군
The spitter. And the guy
who enjoyed my name so much...
날 부를 때마다 이름 갖고
장난치는 놈도 있었지
... he made a noise
every time he said it.
반가워요, 챈들러 빙
삥!
"Nice to meet you, Chandler Bing.
Bing!"
집 좋은데요, 챈들러 빙
삥!
"Great apartment, Chandler Bing.
Bing!"
- 내일은 몇이나 보러 와?
- 두 명
-How many more tomorrow?
-Two.
사진작가란 녀석은
멍청해 보이고
This photographer
who seemed really dull...
배우란 놈은 전화했길래
'전 챈들러 빙!... '하고 받았더니
...and this actor guy
who I'm not sure about.
When I answered
the phone "Chandler Bing"...
'메시지 한번 짧네'하더군
... he said, "Whoa! Short message!"
오빠, 발 안 내리면
다신 못 오게 한다
Foot on the floor
or come over no more.
Your dresser is missing,
but this she notices.
가구 없어진 건 모르면서
이런 건 잘도 봐
-What?
-I have to go.
- 뭐?
- 그만 가볼게
Carol should be home by now, so....
캐롤이 올 때가 됐거든
-How's it going with you guys?
-Better, actually.
- 둘이 요즘은 어때?
- 좋아
뭐가 문제였는지
해답을 찾았어
I finally figured out why we're
having so much trouble.
정말?
-Oh, really?
-Yeah. You know how I have you guys?
나랑 달리 캐롤한텐
친한 친구가 없었거든
She doesn't have any close
friends that are just hers.
근데 지난 주 체육관에서
수잔이란 여자를 만나더니
But last week, she met this woman
at the gym, "Susan" something.
And they really hit it off, and
I think it's gonna make a difference.
아주 죽이 잘 맞아
이제 뭔가 달라질 거야
음... 에릭?
주로 어떤 사진을 찍죠?
So, Eric...
...what kind of photography do you do?
패션 사진이요
Oh, mostly fashion.
모델들이 가끔 올지 몰라요
괜찮겠죠?
There may be models here sometimes.
I hope that's cool.
Yes, that is cool.
괜찮고 말구요
Because I have models here,
you know...
모델이 여기 오면...
처음이라서...
... never.
During the summer I spend most
weekends at my sister's beach house...
여름엔 거의 여동생
해변 별장에서 지내는데
...which you're welcome to use.
같이 가도 돼요
Although I should tell you,
she's a porn star.
미리 말해두지만
걘 포르노 배우예요
Well, I still have
one more person to meet.
집 보러 올 사람이 한 명
더 있지만 여동생 덕분에...
But unless it turns out
to be your sister...
... I think your chances
are pretty good.
보나마나겠어요
All right.
좋아요
Bedroom, bathroom, living room.
침실, 욕실, 거실
여긴 주방이에요
This here is the kitchen,
and thanks for coming by. Bye-bye.
반가웠어요, 잘 가요
뭐 물어볼 거 없어요?
Don't you wanna ask me
any questions?
Sure.
그러죠
What's up?
안녕하쇼?
Well, I'm an actor.
난 배우이고 깔끔하고
TV도 있어요
I'm fairly neat.
I got my own TV.
Oh, and don't worry, I'm totally
okay with the gay thing.
그리고 게이에 대해
전혀 편견 없어요
What gay thing?
게이라뇨?
Just, you know, in general.
The whole "people-being-gay" thing.
게이면 어떻고
아니면 어때요?
전 상관 안 해요
Totally cool with that.
Okay, Jerry.
Thanks for stopping by.
제리, 와줘서 고마워요
- 안녕
Oh, my God!
세상에!
Hey, Mon.
- 안녕, 모니카!
- 안녕
-Wanna hear something that sucks?
-Do I ever!
- 기분 잡치는 소식 들려줄까?
- 그거 좋지
-Chris says they're closing the bar.
-No way!
- 크리스가 여기 문닫을 거래
- 안돼!
- 커피숍으로 바뀔 거래나봐
- 겨우 커피숍?
They're turning it into
a coffee place.
Just coffee?
-Where are we gonna hang out?
-You got me.
- 그럼 우린 어디로 가라고?
- 그러게
-Can I get a beer?
-Did you pick a roommate?
맥주 한 병 줘요
- 룸메이트 결정했어?
- 그럼
-You bet.
-ls it the ltalian guy?
- 그 이탈리아 남자?
- 아마 그럴걸?
Yeah, right.
너무 귀엽더라
He's so cute.
걔랑 다니면 남들이 나한텐
'웃기게 생긴 놈' 그러겠지
That's what I want.
A roommate I can walk around with...
...and be referred to
as "the funny one."
저기 자리 났다
금방 올 테니까
Table's free. Rack them up.
Back in a minute.
깨질 준비나 하고 있어
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
그런 다음
한 게임 치는 거지?
Okay, but after that,
we're shooting some pool.
아뇨, 잠깐만요
Excuse me? Hello? Hi.
아가씨! 여기요
제 친구는 올리브 말고
양파술을 시켰고
My friend ordered an onion...
... not an olive.
전 다이어트 럼콕을
시켰는데 잘못 왔어요
And I ordered a rum and Diet Coke...
...which I don't think this is.
-I am so sorry.
-That's all right.
- 정말 죄송해요
- 뭘요
How hard is it to get a couple
drinks right, huh?
저게 뭐가 어렵다고
버벅댈까?
I would like to propose a toast...
우리 건배해야지
...to the woman who, in one year
from today, will become...
1년 뒤 배리 바버 박사님의
사모님 되실 숙녀분을 위하여!
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Barber, D. D.S.
I think it's time
to see the ring again.
이쯤에서 반지를
다시 봐야겠지?
평생을 함께 할 남자친구가
생긴다니 너무 좋지 않니?
Isn't it exciting? I mean,
it's like having a boyfriend for life!
Yeah. I know.
그래, 맞아
What?
왜?
Oh, I don't know.
글쎄...
Well, maybe it's just the idea...
평생 동안 배리한테만
묶여있어야 된다니...
...of Barry for the rest of my life.
I don't know, I think l....
하룻밤 내 온몸을 내던지고
아주 불살라버리고 싶다니까
I feel like having
one last fling...
...just to sort of get it
out of my system.
- 레이첼, 관둬
- 짓궂기는!
-Rachel, stop!
-You're so bad!
농담 아냐
진짜로 그 뭐랄까...
I'm serious. I really think
I need to just have...
...some meaningless sex,
you know?
옆의 남자 아무하고나
그냥 해버리고 싶어
With the next guy I see.
실례합니다
공을 떨어뜨리고 말았네요
Excuse me, I seem to have
dropped my ball.
Yeah, so?
그래서요?
And now I've picked it up again.
다시 주웠구요
웬일이야!
쟤 고등학교 동창인데
My God!
I went to high school with her.
레이첼!
안녕?
모니카?
잘 지냈어?
Look! Hi! What do you think?
- 이것 좀 봐
- 세상에!
Oh, my God!
You can't even see
where the Titanic hit it.
타이타닉에 부딪혀도
멀쩡하겠다
Yes, his name is Barry.
He's a doctor, thank you very much.
배리라는 사람이고
의사야, 고마워
Just like you always wanted.
Congratulations.
소원 성취했구나
축하해
고마워, 넌 어때?
만나는 사람 있어?
Thank you. So how about you?
Are you seeing anybody?
지금은 없어
Not right now.
Oh, well, that's okay.
괜찮아
I know.
알아
그럼 난 일행이 있어서...
So I think I'll get back
to my friend.
Oh, yeah. Sure, sure, sure.
그래, 그래야지...
우리 언제 만나서
점심이나 먹자
Can we have lunch
the next time I'm in the city?
- 그거 좋지
- 그래
That'd be great.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
- 안녕
Ten bucks says I never see
that woman again in my life.
쟤를 또 만나면
내가 성을 갈지
정말이야
괜찮다니까
No, honey, really. It's fine.
Just...
수잔이랑 같이 가
정말로...
...go with Susan.
Really, I think
I think girls' night out
is a great idea.
여자끼리 밤새는 거 좋지
그래, 안녕!
Okay. Okay. Bye.
-What are they doing?
-I don't know. Something girly.
- 뭐 할 거래?
- 몰라, 여자들 일이겠지
Hey, you're early.
일찍 왔네
What are you doing with the lamp?
램프는 왜?
Just taking it to get rewired.
수리 좀 맡기려고
오디오 맡긴 집엔 가지 마
일주일 째 소식도 없잖아
Don't take it where you took the
stereo. They've had that over a week.
아녜요, 헤클스 씨
아무도 안 떠들었어요
Mr. Heckles, no one is making
any noise up here.
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
오보에 연습에 방해 돼
- 오보에 안 부시잖아요?
- 불 수도 있지
-You don't play the oboe.
-I could play the oboe.
그럼 저도 조용하라고
할 수 있겠네요
Then I'm gonna have to ask you
to keep it down.
Who are you?
누구쇼?
-I'm Eric, Chandler's new roommate.
-I'm Chandler's new roommate.
챈들러의 새 룸메이트
에릭이에요
내가 새 룸메이트인데
-I don't think so.
-I could be Chandler's new roommate.
- 아닐 텐데요
- 될 수도 있지
-But he told me over the phone
-He told me in person.
- 챈들러가 전화로...
- 나한텐 직접 얘기했지
That's weird.
참 이상하네
난 그만 새 집으로
들어가야겠어
I'm going to go into
my new apartment now.
Hi again.
또 만나네요
안녕?
안녕
Thank you so much.
너무 고마워
Don't thank me.
Thank the jerk that never showed up.
약속해놓고 안 나타난
나쁜 놈한테나 감사해
Okay, I gotta get to work.
난 출근한다
-You want some help?
-No, thanks. I got it.
좀 도와줄까요?
아뇨, 괜찮아요
아이고, 이런!
No, I don't!
You okay?
- 안 다쳤어요?
- 네
빨리 일어나느라
중심을 잃었어요
I stood up too fast.
Got a little head rush.
It's the heat.
뜨겁네요
And the humidity.
축축하기도 하고
That's...
환상적인 조합이네요
...a tough combination.
Do you want to come in
for some lemonade?
레모네이드 한잔할래요?
Like you wouldn't believe.
거절할 이유가 없죠
와! 집 좋네요
This is a great place.
Thank you.
고마워요
Just make yourself comfortable.
편히 계세요
Gotcha.
그러죠
So this place is really
my grandmother's.
원래는 할머니 집이에요
이사가셔서 제가 대신 살죠
전 이런 집 구할 형편 못 돼요
I got it when she moved to Florida.
Otherwise I could never afford it.
So if the landlord ever asks...
집주인한테 전 비디오 하나
못 켜는 87세 노파로 돼있죠
... I'm an 87-year-old woman who's
afraid of her VCR. You thirsty?
- 목마르죠?
- 왜 아니겠어요?
You bet I am!
Okay...
자, 여기...
... here's your penis!
Oh, my God!
What the hell are you doing?
지금 뭐 하는 거예요?
레모네이드 한잔
주겠다면서요?
You said, "You wanna come in
for some lemonade?"
그래서요?
So?
진짜 레모네이드
준다는 거였어요?
Were you just gonna give me lemonade?
그럼요!
- 빨리 가리기나 해요
- 네, 미안해요
Cover yourself up!
Oh, right. Sorry.
God, I don't believe this!
별일이야!
Someone asks you in for lemonade
and that means they want to have sex?
레모네이드 마시자면
섹스하자는 뜻이 돼나?
보통은 그렇죠
Usually, yeah.
Well, not just lemonade.
레모네이드뿐 아니라
아이스 티나 주스도 되죠
Iced tea, sometimes juice.
Look, sorry. I just
미안해요
I thought you liked me.
날 좋아하는 줄 알았죠
내가 미쳤지!
I'm such a jerk.
괜찮아요
It's okay.
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
실수할 수도 있죠 뭐
좀 심하긴 했지만요
Not anyone I know, but....
By the way, I can still see it.
근데 아직도 보이거든요
피비!
Where's your bed?
네 침대 어딨어?
여기 없니?
It's not in the apartment?
맙소사!
I can't believe this
is happening again.
이런 일이 또 생기다니!
-What?
-Okay, enough with the third degree!
뭐?
이젠 거짓말도 지겨워
나 여기서 안 살아
I don't live here anymore.
-What are you talking about?
-I'm sorry.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 미안해
그게...
I don't live here anymore.
여기서 안 산다니까
말 안 해서 미안한데
딴 사람들은 다 알아
I didn't know how to tell you.
But, you know, everybody else knows.
Everybody knows?
나만 빼고 다?
That was supposed to be a good thing.
I forget why.
그게 좋을 것 같았거든
이유는 까먹었지만
모니카, 나 있지...
Do you know I couldn't sleep
for a month...
쿠션에 잉크 한방울 떨어뜨리곤
불안해서 한달 간 잠도 못 잤어
...because I got a dot of ink
on one of the sofa cushions?
You could've just turned
the cushion over.
그냥 뒤집어놓으면 됐잖아
반대쪽에 엄청 큰
스파케티 얼룩만 없었어도...
I would have, but I had
a spaghetti stain on the other side.
What?
뭐?
바로 이거야
This is what I'm talking about.
난 맘껏 흘릴 자유를
원한다구!
I need to live in a land
where people can spill!
흘려도 돼
Well, you can spill.
In the sink.
하수구에는...
Oh, honey. It's not your fault,
you know. This is who you are.
모니카...
네 탓이 아냐
그 부분이 나랑
안 맞을 뿐이지
And I love you.
And I want us to be friends.
계속 좋은 친구로 지내려면
떠나는 게 좋을 것 같아
And if I stay here,
I don't see that happening.
- 아쉽다
- 그래
-I love you too.
-Good.
What?
뭐야?
슬퍼하고 있는데 왜?
What? I'm just sad.
No, you're not.
You're wondering which cushion it is.
어떤 쿠션일까
궁금해하고 있지?
- 뭐 보고 있어?
- SOS 해양 구조대
So what are you watching?
Baywatch.
What's it about?
무슨 내용인데?
Lifeguards.
인명 구조대
Well, it sounds kind of stup
뻔한 얘기겠...
Who's she?
누구야?
Nicole Eggert.
니콜 에거트
We like her.
죽여주지
Wow! Look at them run!
뛰는 것 좀 봐!
줄창 뛰지
They do that a lot.
Hey, you want a beer?
맥주 마실래?
- 내가 가져올게
- 일어나지 마
-I'll get one.
-Don't get up. I got a cooler here.
여기 있어
좋았어
- 안녕
- 왔어?
Do you have any beers?
We're out of beers.
맥주 있으면 좀 줄래?
Help yourself.
가져가
You okay?
무슨 일 있어?
Phoebe moved out.
피비가 나갔어
그래
Right.
I don't understand.
이해가 안돼
Am I so hard to live with?
Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
내가 사람을 그렇게 들들 볶아?
- 그래서 애인도 없는 건가?
- 아냐
You don't have a boyfriend because....
네가 애인이 없는 건...
I don't know why
you don't have a boyfriend.
왜 없는지 모르겠네
빨리 하나 만들어야겠다
You should have a boyfriend.
그거야 알지
I think so.
Come here.
이리 와
Listen, you are one
of my favorite people...
넌 내가 제일 아끼는 친구고
...and the most beautiful woman
I've ever known in real life.
현실 세계 사람 중에서
제일 예뻐
안녕
Where is everybody?
아무도 없네
문 닫았지, 크리스가
문 잠그라고 열쇠 줬어
It's already closed. Chris gave me
the keys to lock up. What is wrong?
근데 왜 그래?
I think my marriage...
나 이제...
결혼 생활 접게 생겼어
...is kind of over.
세상에! 왜?
Oh, no! Why?
Because Carol's a lesbian.
캐롤이 레즈비언이야
근데 난 아니거든
And I'm not one.
And apparently it's not
a mix-and-match situation.
우린 물과 기름이라고
할 수 있지
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
I don't believe it!
믿을 수가 없어
Oh, you poor bunny.
가엾어라
I'm an idiot.
내가 바보지
눈치챌 만도 했거든
I mean, I should have seen it.
같이 외출했을 때
예쁜 여자가 지나가면
I mean, Carol and I would be out,
and she'd see some beautiful woman...
...and she'd be "Ross! Look at her!"
캐롤은 이래
'로스! 저 여자 봐'
And I'd think...
난 속으로 그랬지
'내 마누라 멋진걸'
... "God, my wife is cool."
Hey, do you think that Susan person
is her lover?
그럼 수잔이란 여자가
애인이야?
Well, now I do!
그렇겠네!
이걸 어째...
I'm sorry.
Seven years!
7년이야!
I mean, we've been together
seven years.
7년 동안 사귀었다구
She's the only woman
who's ever loved me.
날 사랑해준
유일한 여자였고
유일하게 나랑...
She's the only woman I've ever....
로스...
기분 좋은데
This is nice.
나도 그렇게 생각해
I know. It is, isn't it?
No, I mean it.
This feels really good.
정말로 감촉이 그만이야
Is it 100% cotton?
순면인가보지?
맞아,
세일 때 산 거야
And I got it on sale too.
I should go.
그만 가볼게, 인명 구조원이
핵폭탄을 제거할 참이었거든
One of the lifeguards was just about
to dismantle a nuclear device.
If you want to get
a drink later, we can.
- 나중에 술 한잔 해
- 그거 좋지
That sounds great.
Oh, and listen, it's gonna be
- 그리고 너도 곧...
- 알아
I know.
고마워
Thanks.
Maybe this wouldn't have happened
if I'd been more nurturing...
내가 좀 더 신경 쓰고
관심 가졌다면
...or I'd paid more attention...
이런 일은 없었을 거야
...or I had a uterus.
차라리 여자였든지...
-I can't believe it.
-I know.
- 믿을 수가 없어
- 그래, 네 잘못 아냐
You know, you don't deserve this.
You don't, Ross.
- 넌 정말 좋은 애야
- 고마워
-You're so good.
-Thanks.
And you're so sweet.
넌 정말 착하고 다정해
-Thanks.
-And you're kind.
Thanks.
고마워
Come here.
이리 와
잠깐만!
Wait, wait, wait.
It's okay.
Wait, wait, wait!
My foot is stuck in the pocket.
- 잠깐!
- 왜?
- 발이 구멍에 걸렸어
- 뭐?
-What?
-I can't get it out.
꺼내지질 않아
That's not something
a girl wants to hear.
그런 말 여자는 싫어해
그러지 마
Come on, don't start.
What?
왜?
Stupid balls are in the way.
공이 깔렸어
Oh, well.
That probably wouldn't have been
the most constructive solution.
건설적인 해결책은
아니었을 거야
얼굴에 초크 묻었어
You have chalk on your face.
You're right. I don't know why
I always thought this was real grass.
로스, 네 말이 맞아
이게 진짜 잔디일 리 없지
오빠, 괜찮아?
Honey, you okay?
My wife's a lesbian.
마누라가 레즈비언이야
Cool!
멋진걸!
Ross, Joey. Joey, Ross.
이쪽은 로스
이쪽은 조이야
정말 다시 왔군요
I can't believe you came back.
아무 말 말아요
Don't say anything.
말도 생각도
하고 싶지 않으니까
I don't wanna speak.
I don't wanna think.
그냥 날 안고 키스하고
사랑해줘요, 지금 당장!
I just want you to take me and kiss me
and make love to me right here...
... right now.
레이첼?
레이첼!
왜?
이 길이 아니잖아
You missed the exit.
Sorry.
- 미안
- 대체 무슨 생각해?
My God, what were you thinking about?
배리 생각...
Barry.